

#### CONTACT ME AT

- Office Address: Valentín Gómez 4828/38 Caseros (B1678ABJ)Provincia de Buenos Aires
- svilla@untref.edu.ar
- www.santiagovilla.com.ar
- in @santiago-villa
- @pyronet
- f @santiago.g.villa
- @sntvilla
- https://cutt.ly/3d4RgjS
- santiagovilla83

#### SKILLS SUMMARY

- •••• Music Composition/Musical Production
- •••• Sound Synthesis
- •••• Digital And Analogue Electronics
- •••• Arduino/Processing
- •••• Python/PureData
- • • Computer architecture
- • • Quantum Computation
- •••• English
- •••• German

# **SANTIAGO VILLA**

### SOUND ARTIST & PROFESSOR

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a sound artist and composer, graduated in Electronic Arts, professor at the university (UNTREF), researcher and academic manager, specialized in electronic synthesis and modular systems. Trained in a transdisciplinary career, I have worked through different artistic and musical development techniques, incorporating technology as a tool and science as a conceptual support.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Co-Director

UNTREF | Oct 2016 - present

 Coordination, planning, and implementation across multiple teams

#### Professor

Artes Electronicas | Jan 2007 - Aug 2020

- Technology of the Sound and Video
- Laboratorio II
- Technology of Music I & II
- Musical Production

#### Director

Sistemas Modulares Nucleo | Jan 2016 - Aug 2020

Development and investigation

#### **EDUCATIONAL HISTORY**

# Master in Technology and Aesthetics of Electronic Arts UNTREF| Jan 2012 - Dec 2014

 Focuses on the crossover between art and technology with great emphasis on the creation of autonomous agents, robotic devices and mechanisms that include robotics.

## Degree in Electronic Arts

UNTREF | Jan 2002 - Dec 2006

 Interdisciplinary training career that covers the field of Arts, Sciences and Technology